Guide to the Victor S. Navasky Papers TAM.594
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX: Subject Files, 1918-2012
  - Levinson, Sanford V.: Articles- "The Democratic Faith of Felix Frankfurter", "Responsibility for Crimes of War", "Fidelity to Law and the Assessment of Political Activity...", 1973, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Levison, Stanley, 1975-1976, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Levison, Stanley: File 1, 1968-2000 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Levison, Stanley: File 1 (II), 1968-2000 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Levison, Stanley: File 2, 1981-1988 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Levison, Stanley: File 3, 1989, undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Levison, Stanley: FOIA Documents (obtained by Navasky in 1989), 1960s (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Libby, Scooter: Copy of character reference written by Leon Wieseltier, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - "Looking Back on Senator Joe McCarthy": Firing Line appearance transcript (with William F Buckley Jr and Hilton Kramer), Jun 29, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Luce, Henry, 1975-2010 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - MacBird! (Barbara Garson play produced by Navasky friend David Dretzin), 1966, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - "Macdonald, Jeffrey R. Dr. v. Joe McGinniss" (includes excerpts from closing argument on behalf of Joe McGinniss), 1987 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - "Macdonald, Jeffrey R. Dr. v. Joe McGinniss": testimony of Joseph Wambaugh, Aug 4, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - "Macdonald, Jeffrey R. Dr. v. Joe McGinniss": testimony of William F. Buckley Jr., Jul 22, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Maier, Debbie, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Manifestos for a New America (articles), 1990-1995 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - McGovern, George: Essay "The Case for Liberalism", 2002 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Media and Democracy Congress, New York City, Oct 17, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Menand, Louis: Essays (The New Republic), 1985-1994 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Menand, Louis: Essays (The New York Review of Books, The Nation, Harper's, Esquire), 1982-1994 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Menand, Louis: Essays (The New York Times), 1986-1993 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Menand, Louis: Essays (The New Yorker), 1991-1994 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Miller, Judith: Articles re: Valerie Plame, confidential sources, 2005-2007 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - "The MLA Style Sheet", 1951 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Morganthau, [Robert M.]: Transcript (partial) of interview, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Moyers, Bill, 2002, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1986, 2004, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1990 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - National Jewish Center for Learning and Leadership (CLAL), 1997 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Neoconservatives, 2002, undated (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Neoliberalism, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - New England Labor News and Commentary, 1986-1989 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - The New Leader, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - The New School: Various Items (Navasky serves on the Board of Governors), 1980, 1994, 2006-2007, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - New Statesman, 1990-1993 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - New Statesman, 1995-1996, undated (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - New Statesman: "Current Troubles", 1957, 1987, 1991-1995 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - New Statesman: "Mostly E-Shareholder Memos", 1993-1995 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - The New York Community Trust Newsletters, Feb 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Newman, Paul, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Notes: Various, undated (Box 84, Folder 4-8)
  - Obama, Barack, 2004-2008 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Ophuls, Marcel, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Organization of American Historians (includes publications Magazine of History and The Best American History Essays 2006), 2005, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Palmer, Julia Reed, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Papp (Papirofsky), Joseph, 1959-1960, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - PhoneWriting, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Pincus, Walter, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Pincus, Walter: (includes Pringle Lecture), 2004, 2012 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - "The Pocket Canons": Navasky-Cerf [Potential] Project on the Bible, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Podhoretz, Norman (Commentary Magazine), 1995 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Postal: Historical Journal Articles, 1958, 1974-1975, 1995-1997, undated (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Postal: "I am Against the Postal Zone Law'" (Page from The Mother's Magazine), 1918 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Postal: John, Richard R. - Writings on the Postal System, 1990-1991 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Postal: Kielbowicz, Richard B. - Writigns on Postal Issues, 1986-1994, undated (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Postal: Memos on Postal Reclassification and Postal History (Scott Sherman), 1995-1996 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Postal: Postal rates, 1990-1991, 2007, undated (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Postal: Postal Service Reclassification Proposal - Kielbowicz, Richard B. "History of Mail Classification..." and interrogating responses (heavily annotated by Navasky), 1995 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Postal: Postal Service Reclassification Proposal - Opposition (American Business Press, Victor Navasky), 1995-1996 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Postal: Postal Service Reclassification Proposal - Postal Rates Commission (PRC) decision, 1996-1997 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Postal: Postal Service Reclassification Proposal - Related materials, 1995-1998 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Postal: Postal Service Reclassification Proposal - Supporters (Time Magazine, Dow Jones, Magazine Publishers of America), 1993-1996 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Postal: Postal Service Reclassification Proposal - Transcripts of testimony of MPA/ABP witnesses (before the PRC), 1995 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Postal: Various articles, 1980-1997, undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Public Advocate Issues: Bus Compliance with Americans with Disabilities Act and Homeless Services Emergency Assistance Hotline, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - "The Privatization Option, A Strategy to Shrink the Size of Government" (The Heritage Lectures, The Heritage Foundation), 1985 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Producing the Past: Making Histories Inside and Outside the Academy (History and Theory Series, Wesleyan University), 1997 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Publication Design, 2005-2007 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Carnegie Council on Ethics and International Affairs-Empire and Democracy Project, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Final Edition (includes note from Wallace Shawn), 2004 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Intellectual Digest, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Publications: Media Industry, 1995, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Media Industry, 2004-2006 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Publications: n+1 prototype, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Newsline (Pakistani), 1989, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Publications: Various, 1990-1996 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Publications: Various, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Publications: Various, 2004-2006 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Publications: Various, 2007-2010, undated (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Publications: The Washington Monthly, 1993, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Publishing Project Proposal (includes paper on "Cooperative Publishing"), 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Publishing Proposals: Background/Research, 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Publishing Proposals: Correspondence, 1973-1975, undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Publishing Proposals: Notes, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Publishing Proposals: Proposals and drafts, circa 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse (Navasky provided expert testimony), 1981 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: "A Brief Summary: The Strange History of the La Costa Litigation" (includes exhibits 1-8), 1975-1980 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: "A Brief Summary: The Strange History of the La Costa Litigation" (includes exhibits 9-15), 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: Bergman's Affidavits, 1974-1978 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: Gerth's Affidavits, 1975-1978 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: Defendants' Affidavits (exclusive of authors), 1975-1978 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: Deposition of Jeff Gerth's by article section, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: Deposition (digest) of Lowell Bergman by article section, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: Fratianno v. Penthouse Defendants' affidavits, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: "Memorandum of Basic Steps Taken...Derived From Deposition Testimony and Affidavits" and index to authors' files, 1981, undated (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Rancho La Costa v. Penthouse: Penthouse witnesses, 1976-1980 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Reinventing Left, 2001, undated (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Role of the Intellectual, 1991-2002, undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Rorty, Richard, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Rosenberg Case (includes material on Carl Marzzani, Freedom to Publish; also Navasky notes), 1960, 1972-1973, undated (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Rosenberg Case: "Julius (the FBI) and Me" (draft) by James Weinstein, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Rosenberg Case: "A Mysterious Date: December 27, 1945" (draft annotated by Navasky of chapter in a book being written by Walter Schneir at the time of his death), 2009 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Rosenberg Case: "New Light on the Rosenberg Case: The Meeropols Talk Back" Socialist Review (Nov-Dec 1983) (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Rosenberg Case: Reuben, William A. review of We Are Your Sons by Robert and Michael Meeropol (includes copy of letter from Michael Meeropol/Rosenberg), 1975 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Rosenberg Case: Schneir, Walter and Miriam (Invitation to an Inquest) and Louis Nizer (The Implosion Conspiracy), 1973, undated (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Rosenberg Case: "Secrecy, Duplicity, Dirty Tricks: The Incomplete Record of the Rosenberg Case" (paper presented by Gerald E. Markowitz to the Organization of American Historians), Apr 1981 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Rosenberg Case: Wexley, John, Sep 1955-1959, undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Rosenberg Case: Wexley, John (author of Judgment of Julius and Ethel Rosenberg) - Correspondence with publisher during writing of book and after, 1953-Aug 1955 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Rosenberg Case: Various, 1995, 2008-2011, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - "Ryan Posters '53-'56", 1956 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Safire, William, 1973, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Santoro, Gene (Guggenheim Fellowship proposal), undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Schiffrin, Andre (small notebook), undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - September 11, 2001: Various articles (some annotated), 2001-2002 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Sheinbaum, Stanley K., 2005 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Sherrill, Robert, 1981, 2005, undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Singer, Daniel, 1970-2000 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Singer, Daniel (The Daniel Singer Millenium Prize), 2001, 2006 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Singham, Archie, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Slate, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Soros, George (New Yorker article preview), 1995 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - "Speculations on the Cancer Phenomena, A Study by Susan Harris" (partial) - concerns dogs, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Speech of John Ralston Saul (Utne Reader Visionfest), 1995 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - "The State of Journalism: Where Are We Going Wrong?" (American Society of Magazine Editors), 1998 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Steinem, Gloria (MS. Magazine), 1998, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Stewart, Potter (article on Supreme Court decision re: Evidence Seizure), undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Stone, I.F., 1985, 1987, 1998, 2006, 2009 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-37078 section 3, 1951-1952 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-37078 section 4, 1952-1953 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-37078 section 5, 1953-1954 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-37078 section 6, 1954-1961 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-37078 section 7 part 1, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-37078 section 7 part 2, 1965, undated (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-37078 section 8, 1965-1972 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files #100-45768, 1940s (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Stone, I.F.: FBI Files HQ 65-60654, 1951, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Stone, I.F.: "I.F. Stone: Encounters with Soviet Intelligence" by Max Holland, 2009 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Studies on the Left (table of contents), 1959-1967 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Sumo Wrestling, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - "Talking Union" lyrics, undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Television ("Broadcastin Law and the Consumer", "Television: Voice of Corporate America" and other items), 1979, 1982, undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - TomPaine.com, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Tribe, Lawrence: Copy of letter to John Conyers re: Electronic Surveillance, 2006 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Trillin, Calvin, 1985, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Truehaft, Jessica Mitford (Decca): "Life Itself-Manship" (booklet), 1956 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Twenty First Century Communications, Inc. (prospectus), 1972 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Van den Heuvel, Katrina, 1981, 1995, undated (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Venn, Mrs. Diggory (Radcliffe College/Publishing Procedures Course), 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Venona: Alger Hiss newspaper articles (includes correspondence), 1993-1997, undated (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Venona: Conference speech, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Venona: First Venona Release, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Venona: Second Venona Release, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Venona: Third Venona Release, volume 1 of 3, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Venona: Third Venona Release, volume 2 of 3, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Venona: Third Venona Release, volume 3 of 3, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Venona: Fourth Venona Release, volume 1 of 4, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Venona: Fourth Venona Release, volume 2 of 4, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Venona: Fourth Venona Release, volume 3 of 4, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Venona: Fourth Venona Release, volume 4 of 4, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Venona: General, 1998, 2001, undated (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Venona: "Venona and Alger Hiss" by John Lowenthal, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Vidal, Gore, 1986-1987 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1980, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Vose, Clement, 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Wakefield, Dan, 2005, 2006 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Weber, Paumer F.: Essays on Thomas Jefferson, John Locke, Thomas Paine and Adam Smith, undated (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: Interview, Nov 13, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: "Karl Marx", undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: "Memo One: The General Framework for Thinking About Our Economy" and "Why Our Economy While Stable is in Difficulty", 1954, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: "The Reminiscences of Palmer Weber" (Columbia University American Entrepreneurs Project) pp.1-125, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: "The Reminiscences of Palmer Weber" (Columbia University American Entrepreneurs Project) pp.126-250, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: "The Reminiscences of Palmer Weber" (Columbia University American Entrepreneurs Project) pp.251-374, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: Talk at University of Virginia on "Birthing Civil Rights", Feb 6, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Weber, Palmer F.: Testimony before Senate Subcommittee - "Interlocking Subversion in Government Departments", 1953, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - "Weekliness", 1997, undated (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Weinstein, Allen, 1979, 2004-2005, undated (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Whitehead, Clay, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - "Who's on First?" Bud Abbott and Lou Costello (printed in Communication Magazine), undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Wilcock, John and "The Ojai Orange", 2004 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - World Policy Institute materials (includes articles re: Cold War), 1994, 1995, undated (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Wright, Marilyn, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Writers Tour of USSR: Notes, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Writings by Others: "After Howard Dean," Carol Elkins, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Writings by Others: "Bush's War," Vincent Bugliosi, undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Writings by Others: "Change" and "Implementation of 'Change,'" Susan Harris, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Writings by Others: "Churchill's Horses and the Myths of American Business," Mord Bogie, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Writings by Others: "Cities Back From the Edge," Roberta Brandes Gratz with Norman Mintz, Sep 1997 (Box 89, Folder 21-22)
  - Writings by Others: Correspondence about, 1976-2004 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Writings by Others: "Country to City: Farmers Markets and CSAs", undated (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Writings by Others: "Crews as 'Freud Basher,'" Eric Gillett, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Writings by Others: Crossing Mandelbaum Gate, Kai Bird (draft portions), Nov 2008-Dec 2008 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Writings by Others: "Dreaming in Spanish", undated (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Writings by Others: Exposed, Mark Schapiro, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Writings by Others: "Flower Delivery," Barbara Finkelstein, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Writings by Others: "Heart of a Lion," Stephana Sander with Robert Rudelson, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Writings by Others: "Journey Through Jess," Dorothy Doyle, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 1-2, Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Writings by Others: "A Justification for the Political Immoralism of Machiavelli's Prince," Silverman, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Writings by Others: "Knocking out Cholera," Howard Markel, Oct 24, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Others: "The Man Who Played God," Abby Mann, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Writings by Others: "Memoirs of a Fiesty Sports Writer," Barbara Long, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Writings by Others: "My Life Takes Up Too Much of My Time," Glenda Watters, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Writings by Others: The Neoliberals by Randall Rothenberg, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 8-11)
  - Writings by Others: [New Haven], Feb 20, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Writings by Others: "A New War," Gip Hoppe, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Writings by Others: "Nicaragua: An Enigma of Blood and Politics," Maria Pallais, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 14-15)
  - Writings by Others: "On the Road, Touch and Go, with D.H. Lawrence," Cesar Vallejo, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Writings by Others: Poems by Lilla Lyon, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Writings by Others: "Policy, Advocacy and Action Organizations", undated (Box 90, Folder 18-20)
  - Writings by Others: "Postal Management...," Aleksander Fajnsztajn, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Writings by Others: "Public Philosophy and the Rule of Law", undated (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Writings by Others: "Saratoga Bill," Zachary Sklar, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Writings by Others: Slippery Characters, Laura Bowder, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Writings by Others: "Stand Back, it's Alive and Hasn't Been Fact-Checked!" Dottie Wilson, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Writings by Others: Tennery, Amy - portfolio of published writings, circa 2006-2007 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Writings by Others: "Three Voting Rights Cases" Thesis by Catherine Harr, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Writings by Others: Toxic Sludge Is Good For You (Book Review and film Treatment by Dustin Beilke), 1996, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Writings by Others: "Unequal Justice: Lawyers and Social Change in Modern America" Auerbach, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Writings by Others: "The Waiting Game," Rachel Morris, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Writings by Others: "World War Now or How Seymour Got His Gun Off," Mack Gilbert, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Young Lawyer For The New Deal by Thomas I. Emerson with inscription by Ruth Emerson (Navasky was research asssistant for Thomas Emerson while at Yale Law School), 1991, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Experts Speak, circa 1990s (Box 110)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Report from Iron Mountain, circa 1990s (Box 110)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Naming Names, circa 1990s (Box 111)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Speeches on Independent Schools, circa 1998-2004 (Box 111)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Alger Hiss and Venona, circa 1998-2004 (Box 111)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Alger Hiss, circa 1998-2004 (Box 112)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Conferences and Speeches, circa 1998-2004 (Box 112)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Experts Speak, circa 1998-2004 (Box 112, Box 113)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Alger Hiss: Research and Alger Hiss Oral History Project, circa 2004 (Box 113)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Naming Names and the Hollywood Blacklist, circa 2004 (Box 113)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Harper Row, circa 2004 (Box 113)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Swarthmore, circa 2005 (Box 114)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Agnese Haury, circa 2006 (Box 115)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: Kai Bird, circa 2006 (Box 116)
  - Research Files from 2016 Accretion: John Lowenthal: Alger Hiss, circa 2006 (Box 116)
- Series X: Audio-Visual Materials, 1976-1996, undated
  This series contains a small collection of audio-visual material, primarily audio cassettes. Most of the cassettes represent interviews conducted by Victor Navasky as a part of his research for Naming Names. Among those interviewed are Frank Donner, Walter Bernstein, Albert Maltz, and Estelle Foreman. Of the twenty audio cassettes associated with Naming Names, sixteen were initially digitized and may be accessed by researchers. Four of the original interview cassettes had no identification and have not been digitized. Among the remaining audio cassettes in this series are a Rosenberg debate held at Swarthmore in 1996 and "A Conversation with I.F. Stone at 80," an event sponsored by The Nation Institute and The New School in 1987. Other formats include one VHS tape - Children of the Left (Eric Stange, 1989) and five reel-to-reel tapes, one of which is labeled "McCarthy."
  - Subseries XA: Audio Cassettes
    - Naming Names - Kaplan, Leon, undated (Box 93, Cd 1-2, Box 91, Cassette 1)
      Access Copies
      An access copy of this recording (2 CDs) is available in box 93 of this collection.
    - Naming Names - Donner, Frank, Apr 19, 1976 (Box 91, Cassette 2, Box 93, Cd 3-4)
    - Naming Names - Foreman, Estelle, undated (Box 91, Cassette 3, Box 93, Cd 5)
      An access copy of this recording (1 CD) is available in box 93 of this collection.
    - Naming Names - Gelman, Milton, undated (Box 91, Cassette 4, Box 93, Cd 6)
    - Naming Names - Gelman, Milton #3, undated (Box 91, Cassette 5, Box 93, Cd 7-8)
    - Naming Names - The Hollywood Ten, undated (Box 93, Cd 9, Box 91, Cassette 6)
    - Naming Names - Lennart, Isobel, undated (Box 93, Cd 10, Box 91, Cassette 7)
    - Naming Names - Maltz, Albert, undated (Box 93, Cd 11, Box 91, Cassette 8)
    - Naming Names - Ritt, Martin and Walter Bernstein, undated (Box 93, Cd 12-13, Box 91, Cassette 9)
    - Naming Names - Sklar [George] and Caspary [Vera], undated (Box 91, Cassette 10, Box 93, Cd 14)
    - Naming Names - Swanson, Gersh, Caryell, Rockford, undated (Box 91, Cassette 11, Box 93, Cd 15-16)
    - Naming Names - Townsend, Leo (1 and 2), undated (Box 91, Cassette 12, Box 93, Cd 17)
    - Naming Names - Townsend, Leo (3), undated (Box 93, Cd 18, Box 91, Cassette 13)
    - Naming Names - Wechsler, James, Apr 30, 1976 (Box 93, Cd 19-20, Box 91, Cassette 14)
    - Naming Names - Clurman, Harold, undated (Box 93, Cd 21, Box 91, Cassette 15)
    - Naming Names - Unidentified, undated (Box 91, Cassette 16)
    - Naming Names - Unidentified, undated (Box 91, Cassette 17)
    - Naming Names - Unidentified, undated (Box 91, Cassette 18)